

Contact

Email

kverenchkhiladzeirakli.personal@gmail.com

Address

Tbilisi, Georgia

Skills

Javascript

Typescript

React

Vue

Svelte

Next.js

Nuxt

Node.js

Express.js

Three.js

React Three Fiber

Redux

Tailwindcss

Jest

Cypress

HTML/CSS

And much more ...

Language

English B2/C1

Russian A2/B1

Irakli Kvernechkiladze

Software Developer

Experienced software developer with 5 years of experience. Skilled in programming, web development, e-commerce, back-end, VR, AR, and video games. Developed core data visualization applications used in **CERN's** largest experiment and presented them at ICHEP2020.

Experience

O 2019 - 2023

CERN

Fullstack Developer

Developed high-level visualization 12 different applications for scientific communities, research groups, and students. Participated in workshops, Demonstrated applications to different groups and teams at **CERN**

Responsibilities:

- Upgraded applications with cutting-edge technologies such.
- Mentored newcomers and teaching them FrontEnd Development.
- Created "CORE" library for multiple applications
- Analyzed and profiled of application performance to identify areas of improvement.
- Optimized loading strategy for models, reducing size, and enhancing app loading speed.
- Participated in code reviews and ensured code quality and best practices.

2023 - 2023

Lookers

Fullstack Developer

Lookers is an ever growing multi-franchise dealer group which represents 34 volume and premium car manufacturers throughout the UK and Ireland.

Responsibilities:

- Developed and maintained web application using React.
- Collaborated with cross-functional teams.
- Participated in code reviews.
- Wrote and maintaining technical documentation.
- Identified and addressing performance issues.

2022 - 2023

Basic-Fit

Fullstack Developer

With over millions of members and more than 1100 clubs, Basic-Fit is the European leader in the low-cost fitness market and the fastest growing fitness brand in Europe.

Responsibilities:

- Developed, maintained, and troubleshoot server side code in SFCC.
- Designed and implemented RESTful APIs and web services.
- Implemented and customized SFCC features such as promotions, pricing, and checkout flows.
- Collaborated with front-end developers to deliver seamless user experiences.

Addition

Education

Currently studying Computer Science in Georgian Technical University

Participation

Teaching students Front-End Developement